quinyx.com 2016-05-14

# Privacy Policy | Quinyx

By using this Website, you are agreeing to the use of your information as described in this Privacy Statement.

**Information collection**

As you visit our Website, you do not have to submit any personal information in order to use the Website. This Website only collects personal information that is specifically and voluntarily provided by you. Such information may consist of, but is not limited to, your name, current job title, company address, email address and telephone and fax numbers.

We may also store and maintain any content that you provide, including but not limited to postings on any blogs, forums, wikis and other social media applications and services that we may provide.

**Information use**

At times, you may provide personal information via this site, for example,

  * to gain access to specific content

  * attend a hosted event

  * respond to a survey

  * request communications about specific areas of interest

In such cases, the information you submit will be used to manage your request and to customise and improve this Website and related services offered to you. We may also use your personal information for marketing purposes, or to send you promotional materials or communications regarding services provided by entities within the Quinyx Network that we feel may be of interest to you. We may also contact you to seek feedback on services provided by entities within the Quinyx Network or for market or other research purposes.

You may at any time request that we discontinue sending you emails or other communications generated in response to your provision of personal information via this Website.

**Disclosure of information to third parties**

We may provide your personal information to other entities within the Quinyx Network in order to provide you with information that could be of interest to you and conduct market or other research. Personal information may also be disclosed to other entities within the Quinyx Network and other third parties in order to respond to your requests or inquiries, as part of a corporate transaction such as a sale, divestiture, reorganization, merger or acquisition, or where those parties handle information on our behalf.

By providing information through this Website, you are consenting to the disclosures described above.

**Blogs, forums, wikis, and other social media**

This Website may host various blogs, forums, wikis and other social media applications or services that allow you to share content with other users (collectively “Social Media Applications”). Any personal information or other information that you contribute to any Social Media Application can be read, collected, and used by other users of that Social Media Application over whom we have little or no control. Therefore, we are not responsible for any other user’s use, misuse, or misappropriation of any personal information or other information that you contribute to any Social Media Application.

**Access to information**

If you would like to request access to your information, to update your details, or unsubscribe from communications you should contact webmaster services using the [contact us](mailto:info@quinyx.com) link. In all cases we will treat requests to access information or change information in accordance with applicable legal requirements.

**Information security**

We have in place reasonable commercial standards of technology and operational security to protect all information provided by visitors via this Website from unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

**Contact us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy while using this Website, please send us an [email](mailto:info@quinyx.com) or call us on 0046-8 611 50 20.
